

CONTACT:

199 Concord Street
Portland, Maine 04103
207-838-1283
williamkatahdin@gmail.com

WEBSITE:

williamjordan.net

GIT HUB:

github.com/William-Jordan

HOBBIES:

Wood Turning
3D Printing
Strategy Games
Building Computers
Backcountry Skiing, Climbing,
Ultimate Frisbee, Slacklining.

REFERENCES

John Hunter – Allen Yarnell Center for Student Success

Program Manager john.hunter@montana.edu

Nadezhda Modyanova – Pennington Educational Research Laboratory

Research Scientist nadezhda.modyanova@montana.edu

Naomi Mermin

Employed me summer 2021 for carpentry projects. naomi@naomimermin.com

William Jordan

I am a junior, pursuing a major in computer science at Montana State University. I am interested in a summer internship where I can develop my professional programming skills. I hope to join a team where I contribute and gain valuable work experience. I am conscientious, hardworking, a team player and bring a can-do attitude.

EDUCATION

Montana State University - Bozeman, MT

2020-2024 (Anticipated degree: Computer Science – professional)

RELEVANT COURSES:

CSCI 232 Data Structures and Algorithms

ESOF 322 Software Engineering

CSCI 338 Computer Science Theory

CSCI 366 Computer Systems

CSCI 443 UI/UX design

CSCI 447 Machine Learning

LANGUAGES

Java (6 years programming experience)

- Machine learning algorithms, Web scraping, browser automation HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL

Pvthon

C/C++

GIT (source control)

SKILLS

Microsoft Excel & Word

SketchUp

Dedicated server hosting & maintenance for gamming applications Framing, renovation, painting, light carpentry

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2021 - Present

Student web developer for the Student Success Center at Montana State University. Full Stack LAMP dev on a small team of fellow students.

05/2022 - Present

Developing a child friendly application for Pennington Educational Research Laboratory's project: "Improving language comprehension via gestures in rural Montana children with language impairment and/or autism". Solo developer of a window's native electron app.

Summers 2019 - 2021

Carpentry, landscaping, painting, framing, shingling, trail maintenance.